I, I...
私は、私は...
I...
私は...
...Do I feel something?
... 私 は 何 かを感じますか?
You are now reminded of the environment in which you belong.
あなたは今、 君の所属の環境を思い出します
just,
ただ、
Do I always watch?
私 はいつも 視聴をしていますか?
Or are you just a little curious?
それとも、 少し興味を持っていますか?
I am in psychotherapy.
私は精神療法を行っています
Do you provide psychotherapy?
精 神 療法を行っていますか?
How do you call it?
どうやって呼んでいますか?
I'm a male doctor.
私は男医です
Does a male doctor provide individualized hypnosis?
男医は、催眠の個案を行っていますか?
Yes, it's a visual inspection method.
はい、視診の方法です
I'm far away, so the other person can't find me.
私 は、距離が遠いので、相手に見つけられないです
Is visual inspection okay?
視診は大丈夫ですか?
Visual inspection is fine.
視診は大丈夫です
Is visual inspection okay?
視診は大丈夫ですか?
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
When there is trust in the patient, treatment can be performed through visual inspection.
相手に信頼があるときに、 視診の方法で治療を行うことがで
I'm coming.
きます
Can treatment be done visually?
視 診の方法で治療を行うことができますか?
I can perform treatment by visual inspection method.
私 は 視 診 の方法で治療を行うことができます
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Can the male doctor see it?
男医の方から見えますか
The body is very good.
身体は非常に良いです
thank you.
ありがとう
In this way, does superior agricultural technology have no influence?
このように上農技は影響を与えないのですか?
That's right.
それは、そうです
The reason is that, like hypnosis, it seems to be moving into a different realm.
理由は催眠と同じく、 別の領域を進めているように見えます
And please let us take a photo.
そして 私たちに撮影を行ってください
And please take a photo for us.
そして私たちに撮影を行ってください
Yes, yes, yes.
はい、はい、はい
And please let us take a photo.
そして 私 た ちに撮影を行ってください
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとう
Hello Nyiros.
ナイイロース、こんにちは
Would you like to briefly introduce yourself?
自分の自分の紹介を簡単にしますか?
I don't like it.
私はナイイ
And I'm a therapeutic hypnotist.
そして 私は療癒催眠師です
I'm currently 28 years old.
現在28歳です
28 years old.
28歳
Are you honest?
正直ですか?
Are you working?
仕事をしていますか?
I'm working.
仕事をしています
You can use your break time to provide help like psychology.
休憩時間を利用して、 心理のような助けをすることができます
Speaking of which, can you also discover your own abilities?
そういえば、 自分の能力を発見することもできますか?
that's right.
そうです
Usually you can talk to your friends.
普段は友達に話を聞くことができます
And just like the guide of life,
そして、人生の導師と同じように、
You can try this part.
この部分を試させることができます
yes.
はい
I didn't try not to watch this part.
私はこの部分を見ないようにしませんでした
I'm a little short.
私は身長が少し悪いです
I'm embarrassed.
私 は恥ずかしいです
Healing has nothing to do with it.
療癒は関係ありません
I can wear whatever clothes I like.
私は、私の好きな服を着ることができる
私の好きな服を着ることができる
I can wear whatever clothes I like.
that's right.
そうです
This is very beautiful.
これはとても綺麗です
The professor is now
教授は今、
What do you do?
何 をしていますか?
Now there is.
今はあります
Does the professor provide treatment?
教授は治療をしていますか?
that's right.
そうです
This is like psychology.
これは心理のようなものです
There's something missing here.
ここには何かがありません
What are the professor's interests?
教授の興味は何ですか?
Typically, you will learn psychological treatment.
通常は、精神的治療を学びます
Divination, hypnosis, etc.
占卜、催眠などです
And it's a psychological book.
そして心理のような書籍です
Read a lot and absorb a lot.
多くを読んで、多くを吸収します
It's popular these days.
この時代は流行っていますね
From now on, this kind of behavior is very popular.
今からは、このような行業が とても流行っています
It's very popular.
とても流行っていますね
The physical strength of modern people is very great.
現代人の壓力はとても大きいです
Treatment is required.
治療が必要です
Let's treat the professor later.
後で教授にも治療をしてみましょう
The video footage is very large.
撮影の映像はとても大きいです
I can help you if you need it.
もし必要であれば、 お手伝いできるように
The process of treatment with the professor is very emotional.
教授との治療の過程は、 気 持ちがとても放鬆しています
The professor has such miraculous powers.
教授はこのような神奇な力を持っています
May I ask about the professor's attitude?
教授の姿勢を聞いてもいいですか?
I am now 34, 1, 26, 35.
私は今、 34、1、26、35です
Does it seem like the viewer doesn't look me in the eye when I'm watching?
私が視聴している時に、 視聴者が目を見ないように見えますか?
Normally, when you are asleep, you cannot open your eyes.
通常、眠りの時は、 目を開けることができません
Yes, but it looks like you can open your eyes.
そう です が、 目を開けることができるように見えます
You will be able to see and be able to open your eyes.
目を開けることができるように見えるようになります
I understand.
理 解 しています
I pray for you all.
皆さんのために、 祈ります
I will help you all.
私は皆さんに助けます
I want to see the heart of the viewer.
私は視聴者の心を見るために
From a normal person.
正常な人からです
Sorry to keep you waiting.
お待たせします
sorry.
ご め んなさい
Professor: How much does your mother love you?
教授は、あなたのお母さんはどのくらい愛をしていますか?
What about this, this, this, and the contents of the visit?
これと、これと、 これ と、 訪問内容に関しては?
If you accept it,
もし、あなたが受け入れる程度で、
As you answer, the frequency of your love.
あなたが答えるように、 あなたの愛の頻率
I think it's almost every day.
ほぼ、ほぼ毎日だと思います
Can you use your powers?
あ なたは、あなたの力を使うことができますか?
I'm charging.
私が充電しています
Are you charging?
あ なたが充電しています?
I use my power to heal others.
私は、他の人を療癒することを、自分の力を使うことをします
I can use it.
私は、それを使うことができます
However, I use the method of charging myself.
しか し、私は自分自身が充電する方法を使います
Is your body in a certain place?
私は、あなたの身体は、較好みのある場所にありますか?
I'm uncertain about that.
私は、それについて、不確かです
You need to see my condition.
私の状態を見る必要があります
But my brain hurts.
でも僕は脳が痛いです
brain?
脳?
yes.
はい
How tall are you?
背は?
back?
背?
There is no back.
背はない
do not have?
ない?
yes.
はい
So, do you have a favorite posture?
では、好きな姿勢はありますか?
attitude of love.
愛の姿勢
Hmm.
う ーん
I like a polite attitude.
私は舒服な姿勢を好きです
However, this posture is difficult.
でも、この姿勢は難しいです
However, this is a nice posture.
しかし、この姿勢は素敵な姿勢です
So, is there a way to achieve this posture through long-distance treatment?
では、この姿勢は、遠距離療養の方法はありますか?
Distance treatment is the method that many live-in clients use.
遠距離療養の方法は、多くの住んでいるお客様の方法です
Clients are not able to attend this treatment face-to-face.
お客様は、この療程を面対面にすることができません
Therefore, use this method.
そのため、このような方法を利用します
Of course, there are limits to effectiveness.
もちろん、効果は限界です
It's not better than the face-to-face method.
面対面の方法よりも良くないです
However, I can help you make it in a short amount of time.
でも、少しだけ、短い時間で作り方を少し助かります
Would you like us to show it to you?
私たちの方から、お客様にお見せしたいと思いますか?
that's right.
そうです
We have one customer.
私たちには一人のお客様がいます
We are here today voluntarily.
私 たちは、今日は自願的にここに来ています
Please try the experience.
経験をしてみてください
We are long-term customers.
私たちは長期のお客様です
We are in the sanatorium today we are here.
私たちは、今日は私たちは、ここに来てる療養室です
Experience your healing.
あなたの療癒を体験してください
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
recently,
最近、
There have been times when my life has turned for the worse.
人 生が悪くなってしまうことを遇ったことがあります
There may be a psychological force involved.
心理的な力の関係があるかもしれません
Something like this can sometimes commemorate an incident.
このようなことは、時々の事件を追悼することができます
When psychological and psychological impressions are deep, subsequent conditions can persist.
心理と心理の印象が深い時に、その後の状態が続くことがで
I'm coming.
きます
Well, let me help you.
では、 お手伝いします
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Let us help you now.
今、お手伝いしましょう
Release your body slowly.
身体をゆっくりと放ってください
My body seems to be getting heavier.
身体が重くなっているようです
Close your eyes.
目を閉じます
Close your eyes and take three deep breaths.
目を閉じたら、3つの深呼吸をします
Then, perform deep breathing motions at my frequency.
そして、私の頻率で深呼吸の動作を行います
May I?
いいですか?
First, take a deep breath.
まず、深呼吸をしましょう
Don't use force, take deep breaths.
力 を使わず、深呼吸をしましょう
Fill the thoracic and abdominal cavities.
胸腔と腹腔を充満しましょう
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸をしましょう
Take at least a deep breath.
最低に深呼吸をしましょう
This is the second one.
2つ目です
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸をしましょう
Let's stop for 3 seconds.
3秒止めましょう
Let's take a breath.
息 を 吸 いましょう
息 を吸いましょう
And take a deep breath.
そして、深呼吸をしましょう
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸をしましょう
深 呼吸をしましょう
Be naturally vulnerable from time to time.
時 々、自然に脆弱になってください
Third.
3つ目
Let's breathe.
呼吸をしましょう
Release yourself with a lot of power with one erte stinky breath.
一erteの臭い呼吸で、自分を多くの力で放ちましょう
Next, imagine a space in your head that you like.
次に、私の頭の中で、あなたが気に入っている空間を想像して
please.
ください
Imagine a space that you like.
あ なた が気に入っている空間を想像してください
You can eat on the grassland.
あ なた は草地で食べることができます
You can eat by the sea.
海辺で食べることができます
You can eat it in the forest.
森林で食べることができます
You can make your own small angle.
あなたが自分の小さな角度を作ることができます
Teacher, I'm really looking forward to it now.
先生、私は今、とても楽しみです
Where did you go now?
あ なた は今どこに行きましたか?
I went back to the child's room.
私は子供のお部屋に戻りました
Did you live in the child's room?
あなたは子供のお部屋に住んでいましたか?
yes.
はい
Did you live in your child's room?
あ なた はあなたはあなたの子供のお部屋に住んでいましたか?
I'm 8 years old.
8歳です
Do you like your room very much?
あ なた のお部屋はとても気に入っていますか?
What do you have in your room?
あ なたのお部屋には何がありますか?
There is my favorite toy in your room.
あなたのお部屋には私の大好きな玩具があります
And then there is the mother of my favorite child.
そして、私の大好きな子供のお母さんがいます
Is your child’s mother looking out for you?
子供のお母さんがあなたを照顧していますか?
yes.
はい
Am I hungry? Am I hungry?
私は、お腹が空いているか、 私 は肚子が空いているか、
The child is looking up to me.
子供は私を照顧しています
It makes me feel at ease.
私 を 安心しています
The time and person in your room is when you feel most at ease.
あ なたのお部屋の時間と人物はあなたの最も安心している時です
Right?
よね?
yes.
はい
However, my mother doesn't show up.
しか し、 私 のお母さんが出ない
why?
なぜ?
Why isn't my mother there?
なぜお母さんが出ないの?
What was your condition and state of mind?
あなたの状態と心情はどんな感じでしたか?
It was sad.
悲しかった
I want to cry.
泣きたい
Please help my mom.
私のお母さんを助けてください
You are 8 years old, right?
あなたは8歳ですよね?
Didn't you know what was going on?
あ なた は何が起きているのか知りませんでしたか?
I didn't chase him.
私は彼を追いかけませんでした
Didn't know if your mom works at home?
あなたのお母さんは家に働いているのか知りませんでしたか?
i don't know.
知りません
Were you sad?
あなたの心情は悲しかったのですか?
yes.
はい
Didn't know you weren't helping your mom?
あなたはお母さんを助けていないのか知りませんでしたか?
yes.
はい
what did you do?
あなたは何をしたのですか?
I chased him.
彼を追いかけました
you chased him.
あなたは彼を追いかけました
But I couldn't see him.
しかし、 彼を見ることができませんでした
Did you ever wonder who your closest neighbor is?
あなたの隣に一番親密な人がいるのか知りませんでしたか?
Have you left again?
あなたはまた離れたのですか?
Didn't you know you were sad about your loss?
あなたは失落して、悲しかったのか知りませんでしたか?
yes.
はい
After your mom leaves, you come back to your room.
あなたのお母さんが離れた後、 あなたは自分の部屋に戻ってき
Did you?
ました か?
yes.
はい
You were crying the whole time.
あなたはずっと泣いていました
You don't know how you want to feel safe at that time.
あ なたはその時のあなたがどのように安心したいのか知りません
Was it?
でした か?
I want to sit on his chest.
私は彼の胸に座っていたいのです
Do I want to hold you and make you feel safe?
あなたを抱えて、あなたを安心していたいのですか?
yes.
はい
Do I want to sit on your chest?
私はあなたの胸に座っていたいのですか?
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
Did you imagine how your mother felt?
あなたはあなたのお母さんの身上の気持ちを想像していましたか?
yes.
はい
Is there something you would like to talk about with your mother?
あなたがあなたのお母さんと話したいことはありますか?
You can imagine in your mind and speak what you want
あなたはあなたの心の想像とあなたが欲しいことを話すことがで
Will you come?
きます か?
You love you and me.
あなたがあなたと私を愛しています
You keep my head quiet.
あなたは私の頭を黙っています
Did your mother sleep with you?
あなたのお母さんはあなたと一緒に寝ていましたか?
You hold me and make me sleep.
あなたはあなたを抱えて、私を眠らせます
I'll put you to sleep.
あなたを眠らせます
yes.
はい
You have a feeling that makes you feel safe.
あなたはあなたを安心する気持ちを持っています
I love sitting on your mother's chest.
私はあなたのお母さんの胸に座っているのを愛しています
I'm imagining you.
あなたを想像しています
your mother was the best person to your mother
あなたのお母さんはあなたのお母さんにとって最高の人だったの
Is it?
ですか?
You are the best person for your mother.
あ なたはあなたのお母さんはあなたのお母さんにとって最高の人
Was it?
だ ったのですか?
yes.
はい
You will be healed from chronic treatment in this space of time.
あ なた はあなたをこの時の空間で慢慢療癒していきます
Your downfall at that time.
あ なた のその時の失落と
To me.
私に
Your mother gave your mother a meal,
あなたのお母さんがあなたの母親に餵したの、
crew, I made your mother's cake.
crew、あなたのお母さんの餵したの
This is big, right?
これ が 大 きいですよね?
Yes, I want to eat you too.
はい、私もあなたのことを食べたいです
In this way, you can stabilize your feelings
このように、あなたはあなたの気持ちを安定させることがで
I'm coming.
きます
During the process, you broadcast slowly.
過 程中、あなたはゆっくりと放送します
And slowly paint your sense of loss.
そして、ゆっくりとあなたの失落感を塗ります
Don't show your mother's help,
あなたの母の助けを見せないように、
Remember what is in your heart.
あなたの心の中にあることを覚えてください
you remember to remember you
あ なた は あ なた のことを覚えておくことを覚えて
please.
ください
Mother's help.
母 の助けを
please don't leave me.
私 を 離さないでください
When you grow up, don't let people leave you.
あなたが長大すると、人たちがあなたを離さないでください
don't let me go
あなたを離さないでください
I can't believe you.
私 はあなたに信じられません
What do you believe?
何を信じる?
What do you imagine in this space?
この空間の中で何を思い浮かべるのですか?
I can think of something.
私は思い浮かべることがあります
When I sleep with my mom, I have to go to my dad's room.
私のお母さんと一緒に寝るとき、私の父の部屋に行くことが
there is.
あります
When I sleep with my mom, I have to go to my dad's room.
お 母さんと一緒に寝るとき、私の父の部屋に行くことが
there is.
あります
that's right.
そう です
Sometimes I go to my father's room, where he is sleeping.
時々私は寝ている、父の部屋に行くことがあります
So, do you ever go see your buddies?
それで、仲間に会いに行くことがありますか?
yes.
はい
For some reason, this child did not understand why the conversation between his father and mother was so difficult.
な ぜか、この子は父と母の会話をとても難しいことをしたのか分
Since it is not from the beginning, it is a different mu...
から ないので、 変 わ ったmu...
They might be fighting.
彼女たちが喧嘩をしているかもしれません
彼 女 た ち が 喧嘩をしているかもしれません
I don't know now.
今は知りません
They are not sad.
彼女たちは悲しみではありません
They are happy and fighting.
彼女たちは幸せで喧嘩をしています
I want to pick a fight with them.
私は彼女たちに喧嘩をしたいと思います
Just like their time.
彼女たちの時のように
They let you broadcast what you like
彼女たちは、あなたが気に入ったことを 放送できるようにする
I'm imagining that.
こと を想像しています
to do that
それ を 行 うこと
I'm imagining.
を 想像しています
tongue
舌
of...
を...
You're better.
あなたの方がよい
舌頭
You're better.
あなたの方がよい
Are your mother's eyes big?
母親の目は大きい?
Mother's eyes?
母親の目か?
Are your mother's eyes sober?
母親の目は地味な?
Great for mothers.
母 親 には 大 き い
She imagines being loved by her mother.
彼 女は母親に愛することを想像しています
Do you love your mother?
母親に愛する?
I prefer you.
私はあなたの方がよい
Let us carry out this process.
私たちはこの過程を営みましょう
Do you love your mother?
母親に愛する?
Mother, please take care of me
お母さん、あなたを照顧してくださって
please.
ください
Mom, please post me.
お 母さん、私を貼ってください
Mom, I'm sorry.
お母さん、ごめんなさい
Is it normal?
普通の状態ですか?
I couldn't talk right now.
私は今、話ができませんでした
It so happens that there is a special treatment process.
偶然、特殊な療養過程があります
It is his action-reaction in his subconscious, pre-conscious mind.
それは、下意識の前意識の中で、彼の行為反応です
me too,
私 も、
Photographed with an old camera.
古 老な撮影機で撮影しています
Mom, you are so amazing.
お母さん、とても素晴らしいです
Is he trying to treat your mouth?
彼は、あなたの口を療養しようと思っていますか?
Really
本当 に
It's wonderful.
素 晴らしいです
How are you feeling now?
今、あなたの気持ちはいかがですか?
It's so wonderful.
とても素晴らしいです
Can your mother include all of you?
お母さんは、あなたの一切を包容することができますか?
When you give yourself a sense of comfort,
あなたは、あなたの安慰感を与える時に、
Want to feel included as a mom?
お 母さんを包容することを感じたいですか?
that's right.
そうです
Can you put it inside your mother?
あなたは、お母さんの中に入れますか?
that's right.
そうです
enter
入
Yes.
れ ます
you are mom
あなたは、お母さん
Can I put it inside?
の 中に入れますか?
Do you want to feel included as a mother?
あ なた は、 お母さんを包容することを感じたいですか?
You brought the medicine.
あなたが薬を持ってくれました